A Guide to the JDR 3rd Fund records FA081
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Miscellaneous Files, 1961-1985; 13; 0.5 Cubic Feet 1 document case
  - The American Federation of Arts, 1980 (Box 306, Folder 2269)
  - Arts in Education Program Staff, 1968-1979 (Box 306, Folder 2270)
  - Bassett Hall, 1979 (Box 306, Folder 2271)
  - Donations to JDR 3rd Fund with Condolence Letters, 1978 (Box 306, Folder 2272)
  - "Fine Arts Market Place" - Publication, 1977 (Box 306, Folder 2273)
  - Investment Advice, 1979-1985 (Box 306, Folder 2274)
  - National Council on Philanthropy, 1976-1977 (Box 306, Folder 2275)
  - Notification of Address Change and Termination of Service, 1979 (Box 306, Folder 2276)
  - Publication - JDR Memorial Service, Riverhead Church, 1978 (Box 306, Folder 2277)
  - Annual Report, 1968-1982 (Box 306, Folder 2278)
  - Annual Report and IRS Form 990-AR, 1978 (Box 306, Folder 2279)
  - 12-Year Report, 1977-1983 (Box 306, Folder 2280)
  - Expenditure Responsibility, 1970-1977 (Box 306, Folder 2281)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Leases, 1965-1980 (Box 306, Folder 2282)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - General, 1973-1980 (Box 306, Folder 2283)
  - Tax Status IRS Ruling - JDR 3rd Fund Inc., 1961-1973 (Box 306, Folder 2284)
  - JDR 3rd Fund Inc. - Financial Statements and Supporting Schedules, 1982-1983 (Box 306, Folder 2285)
  - Slides - Miscellany, 65 slides; photographs (Box S 2, Folder 9)
  - Slides - Miscellany, 257 slides; photographs (Box S 3, Folder 10)
- JDR 3rd Fund Annual Reports, 1970, 1973-1978; 14; 7 Bound Volumes
  Related Materials
  Additional annual reports can be found in Series 12: General Records.
  Annual reports
  - JDR 3rd Fund Annual Report 1970 (Item REF 361.74 JOH 1970)
  - JDR 3rd Fund Annual Report 1973 (Item REF 361.74 JOH 1973)
  - JDR 3rd Fund Annual Report 1974 (Item REF 361.7 HOH 1974)
  - JDR 3rd Fund Annual Report 1975 (Item REF 361.7 JOH 1975)
  - JDR 3rd Fund Annual Report 1976 (Item REF 361.74 JOH 1976)
  - JDR 3rd Fund Annual Report 1977 (Item REF 361.74 JOH 1977)
  - JDR 3rd Fund Annual Report 1978 (Item REF 361.74 JOH 1978)
- JDR 3rd Fund photographs, 1968-1977; 1040
  Photographs
  - Youth Task Force - General Correspondence - Harlem Youth Foundation, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 197)
  - Youth Task Force - Publications - National Dialog Conference, Palo Alto, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 198)
  - International Secretariat for Volunteer Services - 1968 Report (Box 15, Folder 199)
  - English Language Teaching in Japan - Committee for Cooperation on English in Japan, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 200)
  - Asian Cultural Program - Sumiko Kiyocka, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 201)
  - Asian Cultural Program - Miscellaneous Photos, 1969-1974 (Box 15, Folder 202)
  - Arts in Education - Jane Remer - Seven Loaves Network, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 203)
  - Arts in Education - Jane Remer - New York Project, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 204)
  - Arts in Education - Jane Remer - Little Rock, September 1975 (Box 15, Folder 205)
  - Arts in Education - Jane Remer - Minneapolis - Site Visit, November 11, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 206)
  - Arts in Education - Jane Remer - Minneapolis - Site Visit, 1977 October (Box 15, Folder 207)
  - Arts in Education - Jane Remer - New York City - Site Visit, 1977 May 13 (Box 15, Folder 208)
  - Arts in Education - Jane Remer - City Center's Young People's Theatre - Showboat, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 209)
  - Arts in Education - Kathryn Bloom - Annual Report, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 210)
  - Arts in Education - Kathryn Bloom - Annual Reports, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 211)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Annual Report, Project Photos, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 212)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Annual Report, Project Photos, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 213)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Annual Report, Project Photos, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 214)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Annual Report, Project Photos, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 215)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Annual Report, Project Photos, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 216)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Annual Report, Projects, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 217)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Annual Report, Projects, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 218)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Annual Report, Project Photos, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 219)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Annual Report, Project Photos, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 220)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Stake, Robert - Evaluating the Arts in Education, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 221)
  - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Little Rock, Arkansas, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 222)
  - Asia Society / CEMREL - Jaipur Observatory - 1974 (Box 17, Folder 222)
  - Baldwin School of Puerto Rico - Photos with Reports, 1970-1973 (Box 17, Folder 223)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Bank Street College of Education - 1969/1970 Report - Portraits of Staff (Box 17, Folder 225)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Bank Street College of Education, 1969/70 Reports, Activities (Tearchers), 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 226)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Bank Street College of Education, 1969/70 Report - School Scenes, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 227)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - ES'70 - Meeting, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 228)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - ES'70 - Portland, Oregon Program, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 229)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Mineola Public Schools - Arts Project Activities (Box 17, Folder 230)
  - Arts in Education - Museum of Modern Art - Children's Art Caravan (Box 17, Folder 231)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - PS 3-M - Final Report, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 232)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Oklahoma City Arts Council, Festival, 1973 April (Box 18, Folder 233)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Ridge Street Schools, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 234)
  - Arts in education - K. Bloom - University City Schools - Project Photos, 1969-1973 (Box 18, Folder 235)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - University City Missouri - Meetings, Summer Workshop, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 236)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - University City Missouri Schools - JDR 3rd visit, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 237)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Institute of American Indian Arts Theatre, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 238)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - National Chorale Council, 1970/71 Season, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 239)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - San Francisco Art Institute, Report, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 240)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Columbia University Center for the Arts, Proposal, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 241)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - University of Michigan Experimental Theatre Festival, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 242)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - University of Southern California Joint Educational Project, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 243)